Roberto Gauna

Software Engineer

Provo, UT 385-2549282

rgauna@gmail.com

Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/rgauna

Github

github.com/rgauna

Portfolio

http://rgauna79.github.io/portfoliorjg

Profile

Full-stack software development with experience in design, installation, testing and maintenance of software systems. Experience in the most cutting-edge development tools and procedures. Able to effectively self-manage independent projects. Good collaboration skills within a productive team.

Education	Skills
(March 2011 – July 2015) UPTP "JJ. Montilla" – Bachelor of Engineering - BEng Computer Science in Acarigua - Venezuela	 HTML5, CSS JavaScript (React) Python, (Django) SQL (MySQL, Postgres) Git - Github PHP (Laravel)

Experience

(November 2021 - Present) Innovative Labs - Preweigh Lead

Department Lead.

(January 2020 - Present) Innovative Labs - Batching technician

- Pre-weighting products
- Batching.

(October 2017 - November 2019) Liberty Press - Binder operator

- Responsible of auto-feeder equipment preparation
- Configure and prepare paper trimmer

(August 2008 - 2017) G&B Sistemas C.A, Customer service and technical service

- OS Technical service
- Software and hardware issues.

(July 2011 - July 2015) Hospital Agua Blanca, Software Developer

- Software Developer
- HTML, PHP, Ajax
- Apache Server, MySQL

Courses

- freeCodeCamp certifications (online) 2023:
 - Responsive web design.
 - JavaScript Algorithms and data structures.
 - Front-end development libraries.
 - Data visualization
- Odin Project (online) 2023:
 - Full-stack JavaScript Course.